### Our Policies

### Our Terms of Service

Privacy Policy
--------------

**Last Updated: March 26, 2024**

This Privacy Policy describes the policies of Omni Development, Inc. dba the Omni Group (collectively “Company” or “we,” “us,” or “Omni Group”) regarding the information we collect or receive about our customers. It is applicable to the [omnigroup.com](https://omnigroup.com/) website and other interactive features, applications, services, or downloads that are operated by the Omni Group and which are available through the websites produced and maintained by us (“Website”). We have established this security and privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) to let you know the kinds of personal information we may gather, why we gather your information, what we use your personal information for, when we might disclose your personal information, and how you can manage your personal information.

Our overall stance is that privacy is a fundamental human right, and your data is yours. We don’t share data gathered from our apps or websites except as necessary to perform the functions you expect us to perform. We do keep track of conversations we have with you so that we can improve our products and services and provide you with good support, and we track connections to our Website to keep it secure. But we try not to collect more information than we need: the less we know about you, the easier it is to ensure your privacy. Within our apps, we give you control over where your data is stored and synced, rather than requiring that you store your data with us.

Along with the personal information which we gather or which you provide to us (for example, when you sign up for a newsletter or other mailing list, you comment on a blog or forum we operate, you purchase something from us, or we provide customer service to you), this Privacy Policy describes our policy regarding files which you upload to or store on the Omni Sync Server (“Customer Data”).

When you provide personal information and/or Customer Data, you are consenting to the manner in which the Omni Group will collect, use, disclose and otherwise manage your personal information and Customer Data, as set out in this Privacy Policy.

If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website, software, or Omni Sync Server. We may modify or amend the terms of our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any material changes that affect your control over your information.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or don’t see your concerns addressed here, you should contact us by email at [info@omnigroup.com](mailto:info@omnigroup.com).

### What Information About Me Is Collected and Stored?

One of the basic principles we’ve tried to follow in designing this Website is that we ask for only the information we need to provide the service you’ve requested. As a result, what information we collect and store depends almost entirely on how you choose to make use of our Website and our services. You may provide the following information to us directly:

* Payment information, including credit card information.
* Content you may include in survey responses.
* Information contained in your communications to us, including call recordings of customer service calls.
* Information you send to us via a social media platform.
* Any information or data you provide by interacting in our online forums and chatrooms, or by commenting on content posted on our Services. Please note that these comments are also visible to other users of our services.
* Information you submit to inquire about or apply for a job with us.

In addition to information which you explicitly and knowingly provide, some information is collected automatically such as:

* Our Website uses browser cookies in order to gather information on usage patterns. These are used to measure how well our site is working, not to track you as an individual.
* Our software may, with your permission, send us anonymous statistics about its use (see below).
* Our servers maintain industry-standard logs of their activity: web page visits, including IP address, Referer: header, and user-agent; envelope information of e-mail sent and received; and the like.

### How do we use the information we collect?

In general, we do not use your information beyond the purpose for which you provided it to us. For example, if you ask us a question by email, or subscribe to a mailing list, we will not send you product announcements or other promotional communications in response (unless that is what you requested). We do not sell, barter, or rent your personal information.

We may use the information we collect for the following purposes.

* To provide you with our products and services, including to take steps to enter a contract for sale or for services, process payments, fulfill orders, send service communications (including renewal reminders), and conduct general business operations, such as accounting, recordkeeping, and audits.
* To improve and grow our products and services, including to develop new products and services and understand how our products and services are being used, our customer base and purchasing trends.
* To provide you with important information about the product or service that you are using, including critical updates and notifications.
* To protect and secure our Website, assets, network, and business operations, and to detect, investigate, and prevent activities that may violate our policies or be fraudulent or illegal.
* To comply with legal process, such as warrants, subpoenas, court orders, and lawful regulatory or law enforcement requests and to comply with applicable legal requirements.

In the event we wish to publicly post any of your personal information on a website (as, for instance, a letter), we will contact you with details and ask for your express permission to publish that information and will not publish without your express permission.

If you have subscribed to any Omni newsletter, you may unsubscribe at any time by following the instructions located within each newsletter and on our Website, or by contacting us.

We gather general non-specific statistics about Customer Data that will help us improve the service, such as the amount of storage you are consuming on our servers, user-agent information sent in HTTP headers, or overall usage patterns. In rare cases we may examine metadata such as file names or synchronization client state to understand how the service is performing.

If you provide information to us for the purpose of making it public (for example, on a mailing list, blog, or forum that we operate), we cannot control what other parties may do with that information once it is public. Please be careful about what you disclose and do not post any information that you expect to keep private.

### How do we share the information we collect?

We occasionally have service providers, subsidiaries, affiliates, and partners perform functions on our behalf, such as marketing, analytics, credit card processing, shipping, or stocking orders, fraud protection, etc. These entities have access to personal information only to the extent needed to perform their functions. They are contractually obligated to maintain the confidentiality and security of that personal information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

We may share any of the information we collect with the following recipients.

* **Service providers**: We engage vendors to perform specific business functions on our behalf, and they may receive information about you from us or collect it directly. These vendors are obligated by contract to use information that we share only for the purpose of providing these business functions, which include:
    * _Supporting service functionality_, such as vendors that support event registration, customer service and customer relationship management, subscription fulfillment, freight services, application development, list cleansing, postal mailings, and communications (email, fax).
    * _Auditing and accounting firms_, such as firms that assist us in the creation of our financial records.
    * _Professional services consultants_, such as firms that perform analytics, assist with improving our business, provide legal services, or supply project-based resources and assistance.
    * _Analytics and marketing services_, including entities that analyze traffic on our online properties and assist with identifying and communicating with potential customers.
    * _Security vendors_, such as entities that assist with security incident verification and response, service notifications, and fraud prevention.
    * _Information technology vendors_, such as entities that assist with website design, hosting and maintenance, data and software storage, and network operation.
    * _Marketing vendors_, such as entities that support distribution of marketing emails.
* **Social media platforms**: If you interact with us on social media platforms, the platform may be able to collect information about you and your interaction with us. If you interact with social media objects on our Website (for example, by clicking on a Facebook “like” button), both the platform and your connections on the platform may be able to view that activity. To control this sharing of information, please review the privacy policy of the relevant social media platform.
* **Government entities/Law enforcement**: We may share information when we believe in good faith that we are lawfully authorized or required to do so to respond to lawful subpoenas, warrants, court orders, or other regulatory or law enforcement requests, where necessary to protect our property or rights or the safety of our employees, our customers, or other individuals, or under emergency circumstances to protect the personal safety of us, our affiliates, agents, the users of the Website, or the public. In cases where we must disclose personal information or Customer Data, we will send an email to the address registered to any accounts affected by that disclosure.

We may provide aggregate, anonymous statistical information derived from information we collect to other organizations or to the public (for example, see [https://update.omnigroup.com/](https://update.omnigroup.com/)). Any information we share in this manner will not identify you personally.

### How long do we retain the information we collect?

We determine the retention period for each of the categories of personal information listed above based on (1) the length of time we need to retain the information to achieve the business or commercial purpose for which it was obtained, (2) any legal or regulatory requirements applicable to such information, (3) internal operational needs, and (4) any need for the information based on any actual or anticipated investigation or litigation.

If you provide your credit card information, we will store the expiration date and last four digits of the credit card number in case you contact us with a billing question or we need to apply a refund or credit. We do not store the full credit card number or the card security code you enter in the payment form.

We maintain backups of Customer Data in order to recover from hardware failures or other problems. These backups are not kept longer than six months.

### What Steps Are Taken To Keep Personal Information and Customer Data Protected?

We are committed to protecting your personal information and Customer Data. We use a variety of technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information and Customer Data from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure.

Personal information we collect or receive and Customer Data you upload is stored in protected operating environments that are not available to the public and, when transmitted, is protected using strong cryptography.

We limit access to your personal information or Customer Data to only our employees and third parties who need access for purposes described in this Privacy Policy. They are contractually obligated to maintain the confidentiality and security of that personal information, are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose, and are subject to disciplinary action, including possible termination and civil and/or criminal prosecution, for failing to do so.

If a password is used to help protect your accounts and personal information and Customer Data, it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. Do not share this information with anyone. If you are sharing a computer with anyone you should always log out before leaving a website or service to protect access to your personal information and Customer Data from subsequent users.

While we use reasonable security measures to safeguard your personal information and Customer Data once we receive it, no transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. You should know that no company, including the Omni Group, can fully eliminate security risks associated with personal information or Customer Data. Accordingly, the Omni Group cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us on our Sites.

Do Not Track: Your browser or device may include “Do Not Track” functionality. We already limit our tracking to that which is necessary to provide our services, and we honor Do Not Track signals we receive from your website browser. Note that the information collection and disclosure practices and the choices that we provide to you will continue to operate as described in this privacy policy regardless of whether a Do Not Track signal is received.

### Is Information Collected From Children?

We do not sell or ship any items ordered through this Website directly to anyone who we know to be under the age of 13, nor do we collect any personal information from anyone who we know to be under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, you should use this Website only with the involvement and consent of a parent or guardian and should not submit any personal information to us. Our Website is not intentionally targeted to children under the age of 13.

### Passwords

To use some features of this Website, or our software, you may be asked to set up an account and provide a functional email address and password. You should be careful about providing your password to others — you are responsible for the actions of anyone you’ve shared your password with. No one at the Omni Group will ask for your password; if they do, you should not provide the information and should email [customerservice@omnigroup.com](mailto:customerservice@omnigroup.com) to report the incident so we can investigate.

### Governing Law

The Website is published in the United States. U.S. law shall govern in any and all disputes, including privacy or defamation issues or otherwise.

### Transfers

If you use our Website outside of the United States, you understand that we may collect, process, and store your personal information in the United States and other countries. The laws in the U.S. regarding personal information may be different from the laws of your state or country. Any such transfers will comply with safeguards as required by relevant law. If applicable, you may have a right to claim compensation for damages caused by a breach of relevant data protection laws.

### Changes to This Policy

As our company and Website continue to develop, we may add new services and features to our Website or products. If these additions affect our Privacy Policy, this document will be updated appropriately. We will post those changes prominently so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. We do, however, recommend that you read this Privacy Policy periodically in case you missed any changes to the Privacy Policy.

### Your Privacy Rights

We will honor the following rights regarding your personal information, regardless of where you reside or whether you are subject to a specific state or region’s data protection laws:

* Access and Portability: Request access to personal data we hold about you or request transmission of your data to a third party.
* Correction: Request that we rectify inaccurate or incomplete personal data we store about you.
* Deletion: Request that we erase personal data when such data is no longer necessary for the purpose for which it was collected, when you withdraw consent and no other legal basis for processing exists, or when you believe that your fundamental rights to data privacy and protection outweigh our legitimate interest in continuing the processing.
* Restriction of processing: Request that we restrict our processing of personal data if there is a dispute about the accuracy of the data; if the processing is unlawful; if the processing is no longer necessary for the purposes for which it was collected but is needed by you for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims; or if your request to object to processing is pending evaluation.
* Objection to processing: Object to processing of your personal data based on our legitimate interests or for direct marketing (including profiling). We will no longer process the data unless there are compelling legitimate grounds for our processing that override your interests, rights, and freedoms, or for the purpose of asserting, exercising, or defending legal claims.
* Transfers: Obtain information about and a copy of the safeguards we use to transfer personal data across international borders.
* Opt out of “sales” or “sharing” of personal information and use of their personal information for “targeted advertising,” as those terms are defined under applicable law. Note that we do not use your personal information for these purposes.
* Opt out of “profiling” under certain circumstances, as defined under applicable law. Note that we do not engage in “profiling,” as defined under applicable law.

You can exercise these rights by contacting us at using one of the methods listed below.

_Additional Information for European Union (EEA), the United Kingdom (UK), and Swiss Residents_

Purposes of processing and legal basis for processing: As explained above, we process personal data in various ways depending upon your use of our products and Website. We process personal data on the following legal bases: (1) with your consent; (2) as necessary to perform our agreement to provide services; and (3) as necessary for our legitimate interests in providing the products and Website where those interests do not override your fundamental rights and freedom related to data privacy.

Right to lodge a complaint: Users that reside in the EEA, UK, or Switzerland have the right to lodge a complaint about our data collection and processing actions with the supervisory authority concerned. Contact details for data protection authorities are available from the [European Commission website](https://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm).

_Additional Information for California Residents_

If you are a California resident, California law permits you to request certain information regarding the disclosure of your personal information by us and our related companies to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. We do not disclose your personal information for this purpose.

### California Consumer Privacy Act

The California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) provides California residents with rights to receive certain disclosures regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of information about them, as well as rights to know/access, correct, delete, and limit disclosure of personal information. You have the right to be free from discrimination based on your exercise of your CCPA rights. To the extent that we collect personal information that is subject to the CCPA, that information, our practices, and your rights are described below.

_Notice at Collection Regarding the Categories of Personal Information Collected_

You have the right to receive notice of certain information about our data collection, use, and disclosure. The following table summarizes the categories of personal information we collect; the categories of sources of that information; and whether we disclose, sell, or share that information to service providers or third parties, respectively. The categories we use to describe personal information are those enumerated in the CCPA. We collect this personal information for the purposes described above in “How do we use the information we collect.”

| Category | Information Type | Source | We disclose to: | We sell to/share with: |
| --- | --- | --- | --- | --- |
| Identifiers | * Contact information or personal characteristics (name; email address; postal address; telephone number; signature)<br>* Social media handles | You; our social media pages; third party subscription service providers | Service Providers | Not sold/shared |
| Financial Information | * Payment card data | You | Service Providers | Not sold/shared |
| Protected Classifications and Other Sensitive Data | * Date of Birth | You | Service Providers | Not sold/shared |
| Commercial Information | * Transaction information<br>* Billing and payment records<br>* Order history | You | Service Providers | Not sold/shared |
| Internet or Electronic Network Activity Information | * IP address<br>* Device identifier (e.g., MAC)<br>* Diagnostic information (e.g., crash logs, performance data) | You; Service Providers | Service Providers | Not sold/shared |
| Professional or Employment-Related Information | * Current employer<br>* Job title | You | Service Providers | Not sold/shared |
| Education Information | * Education history<br>* Level of education | You | Service Providers | Not sold/shared |
| Content of Communications | * Contents of phone calls, emails, or text messages<br>* Photos | You | Service Providers | Not sold/shared |

Entities to whom we disclose information for business purposes are service providers, which are companies that we engage to conduct activities on our behalf. We restrict service providers from using personal information for any purpose that is not related to our engagement.

_Your rights under the CCPA_

* _Opt out of sale or sharing of personal information_: You have the right to opt out of our sale or sharing of your personal information to third parties. We do not sell or share your personal information to third parties. Your right to opt out does not apply to our disclosure of personal information to service providers.
* _Limit the use of your sensitive personal information_: You have the right to limit our use of your sensitive personal information if we use such information to infer characteristics about you. We do not use your sensitive personal information for this purpose.
* _Know and request access to and correction or deletion of personal information_: You have the right to request access to personal information collected about you and information regarding the source of that personal information, the purposes for which we collect it, and the third parties and service providers to whom we sell, share, or disclose it. You also have the right to request in certain circumstances that we correct personal information that we have collected about you and to delete personal information that we have collected directly from you. Please contact us to exercise these rights.

_Additional Information for Nevada Residents_

Residents of the State of Nevada have the right to opt out of the sale of certain pieces of their information to third parties. We do not engage in such sales. If you are a Nevada resident and would like more information about our data sharing practices, please contact us.

**Procedures For Exercising your Rights**

If you have previously opted to subscribe to an Omni mailing list, you may always opt-out of receiving future e-mail messages and newsletters by ending your subscription. Unsubscribe instructions are located within each newsletter and on our Website, or you may contact our Customer Service Department.

You have the right to know about the personal information we have collected about you, as well as access and correct such information and delete personal information that you have previously provided to us. You can request to know, access, correct, update, or request the deletion of certain personal information by emailing [support@omnigroup.com](mailto:support@omnigroup.com) or [sales@omnigroup.com](mailto:sales@omnigroup.com).

If you wish to cancel your password, please contact our Customer Service Department by email at [support@omnigroup.com](mailto:support@omnigroup.com) or by phone at 800-315-6664. If you become aware of any unauthorized use of your password, data theft, or possible security issues with our Website or products, please contact [security@omnigroup.com](mailto:security@omnigroup.com). Especially sensitive issues may be encrypted to our PGP key, `0x0A70467B`.

You may, under certain circumstances, authorize another individual or a business, called an authorized agent, to make requests on your behalf. (Authorized agents in California must be registered with the California Secretary of State.)

**Verification**: We must verify your identity before responding to your request. We verify your identity by asking you to provide personal identifiers that we can match against information we may have collected from you previously. We may need to follow up with you to request more information to verify identity.

We may have a reason under the law why we do not have to comply with your request, or why we may comply with it in a more limited way than you anticipated. If we do, we will explain that to you in our response.

**Appeals**: If your request is denied, you may appeal the denial by contacting us as described in the notice of denial.

**Who do I talk to if I have more questions?**

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to [info@omnigroup.com](mailto:info@omnigroup.com).

[Mastodon

Mastodon](https://mastodon.omnigroup.com/@OmniGroup)[Facebook

Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/theomnigroup/)[Instagram

Instagram](https://www.instagram.com/omnigroup/)[Slack

Slack](https://www.omnigroup.com/slack/)[Forums

Forums](https://discourse.omnigroup.com/)

### Products

* \-

### Resources

### Company

© 1994–2024 The Omni Group; Apple, MacBook, the Apple logo, iPad, iPhone, Apple Watch, and App Store are trademarks of Apple Inc., registered in the U.S. and other countries and regions. Apple Vision Pro is a trademark of Apple Inc.
